<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>public policy on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/categories/public-policy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in public policy on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/public-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Public Policy | 公共政策分析 (30700953)</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/01-analysis_of_public_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/01-analysis_of_public_policy/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of Public Policy: Perspectives and Methods focuses on empirical policy evaluation. The course introduces a political scientist view and a series of modern empirical methods into public policy analyses. Students will learn not only the fundamental analytic theories for public policy evaluation but also tools such as case study, survey, experiments, and big-data analysis, that can be used to analyze different types of policies. In every topic, we will include real-life cases to illustrate how the theories and method can be applied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Policies | 理解公共政策 (10700193)</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/01-understanding_public_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/01-understanding_public_policy/</guid>
      <description>Policies are everywhere in the modern society. They serve as the tie between the rulers and ruled and the means to steer collective actions for the given goals. In this sense, the ability to understand where policy comes from and how it runs and ends has become a crucial quality of the potential successors and leaders. Understanding Public Policies: Interdisciplinary Perspectives and Case Illustrations is the place you cultivate this quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urban Politics | 城市政治学</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/03-urban-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/03-urban-politics/</guid>
      <description>This course concentrates on the dominant force of human modernization&amp;mdash;the cities. From a view of political science, the course discuss the macro and micro politics among heterogeneous cities together with specific topics of urban governance. The course is on building. More information will be available soon.
Preview Slides     TBA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Linguistics</title>
      <link>/project/polilingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/polilingua/</guid>
      <description>Language is the fundamental feature of human beings. The debate of whether does language shapes thoughts or the other way around has inspires the greatest theorists and scientists throughout the human history. Nevertheless, the importance of language in political lives has not been well studied yet.
Cutting in from an empirical angle, I strive to identify the influences of linguistic relativity and language planning in the government-mass relationship and the (re)construction of mass political cognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Response</title>
      <link>/project/poliresponse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/poliresponse/</guid>
      <description>Disproportionate scholarly attention in the studies of the government-mass relationship focused on the government&amp;rsquo;s responses (motivations and means) to public demands. Less research explores what happens next. However, in real politics, the governments often fall into the curse that what they do mismatches what the public wants. I unbox this puzzle by investigating how the public responds to the government&amp;rsquo;s response. Several focused questions include: what do the masses learn from the government&amp;rsquo;s decisions and actions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Science: Substantive Topics</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/</guid>
      <description>** No content below YAML for the series _index. This file is a leaf bundle, and provides settings for the listing page layout and sidebar content.**</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
