<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R Packages on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R Packages on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>interplot</title>
      <link>/software/interplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/interplot/</guid>
      <description>Solt, Frederick, and Yue Hu. 2015. interplot: Plot the Coefficients of Variables in Interaction Terms. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  interplot is a tool for plotting the conditional coefficients (&amp;ldquo;marginal effects&amp;rdquo;) of variables included in multiplicative interaction terms. The function plots the changes in the coefficient of one variable in a two-way interaction term conditional on the value of the other included variable. The resulting plot also includes simulated 95% confidential intervals of these coefficients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dotwhisker</title>
      <link>/software/dotwhisker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/dotwhisker/</guid>
      <description>Solt, Frederick, and Yue Hu. 2015. dotwhisker: Dot-and-Whisker Plots of Regression Results. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
 dotwhisker is an R package for quickly and easily generating dot-and-whisker plots of regression results, either directly from model objects or from tidy data frames. It provides a convenient way to create highly customizable plots for presenting and comparing statistics. It can be used to plot coefficients or other estimates (e.g., predicted probabilities) within a model or compare them across different models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>regioncode</title>
      <link>/software/regioncode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/regioncode/</guid>
      <description>Hu, Yue et al. 2020. regioncode: Convert Region Names and Division Codes of China Over Years. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  Inspired by Vincent Arel-Bundock&amp;rsquo;s well-known countrycode, we created regioncode to achieve similar functions specifically for China studies. regioncode enables seamlessly converting regions&amp;rsquo; formal names, common-used names, and administrative division codes between each other.
To install:
 the latest released version: install.packages(&amp;quot;regioncode&amp;quot;). the latest developing version: remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/regioncode&amp;quot;).  More details are available at:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drhur</title>
      <link>/software/drhur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/drhur/</guid>
      <description>Yue Hu. 2016. drhur: Learning R with Dr. Hu. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  drhur is pedagogical software make the R learners&amp;rsquo; life a little bit easier and more happily and a supplementary courseware for Dr. Yue Hu&amp;rsquo;s R program lectures. The tutorials included are crystallized during Dr. Hu&amp;rsquo;s online and offline R workshop.
To install:
 the latest release version: install.packages(&amp;quot;drhur&amp;quot;).   the latest version: remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/drhur&amp;quot;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drhutools</title>
      <link>/software/drhutools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/drhutools/</guid>
      <description>A toolbox for writing an academic paper with rmarkdown. The tools includes data analyses, visualization, and documenting.
To install:
 the latest released version: install.packages(&amp;quot;drhutools&amp;quot;). the latest developing version: remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/drhutools&amp;quot;).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pewdata</title>
      <link>/software/pewdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/pewdata/</guid>
      <description>Solt, Frederick, and Yue Hu. 2016. pewdata: Reproducible Retrieval of Pew Research Center Datasets. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  
pewdata is an R package that provides reproducible, programmatic access to survey datasets from the Pew Research Center.
To install:
 the latest released version: install.packages(&amp;quot;pewdata&amp;quot;) the latest development version:  if (!require(ghit)) install.packages(&amp;#34;ghit&amp;#34;) ghit::install_github(&amp;#34;fsolt/pewdata&amp;#34;) Note that pewdata depends on the Firefox browser; if you don&amp;rsquo;t already have it installed on your machine, get it here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
