<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo-Site on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/tags/hugo-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo-Site on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/hugo-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Public Policy | 公共政策分析 (30700953)</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/01-analysis_of_public_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/01-analysis_of_public_policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.gif&#34; width = &#34;350&#34; height = &#34;330&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analysis of Public Policy: Perspectives and Methods focuses on empirical policy evaluation.&#xA;The course introduces a political scientist view and a series of modern empirical methods into public policy analyses.&#xA;Students will learn not only the fundamental analytic theories for public policy evaluation but also tools such as case study, survey, experiments, and big-data analysis, that can be used to analyze different types of policies.&#xA;In every topic, we will include real-life cases to illustrate how the theories and method can be applied.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Policies | 理解公共政策 (10700193)</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/01-understanding_public_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/01-understanding_public_policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.gif&#34; width = &#34;350&#34; height = &#34;330&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Policies are everywhere in the modern society.&#xA;They serve as the tie between the rulers and ruled and the means to steer collective actions for the given goals.&#xA;In this sense, the ability to understand where policy comes from and how it runs and ends has become a crucial quality of the potential successors and leaders.&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Understanding Public Policies: Interdisciplinary Perspectives and Case Illustrations&lt;/em&gt; is the place you cultivate this quality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
