<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HU Yue | 胡悦, Ph.D. on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HU Yue | 胡悦, Ph.D. on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Political Data | 政治数据分析 (70700173)</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/01-analysis_of_poli_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/method-series/01-analysis_of_poli_data/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.gif&#34; width = &#34;350&#34; height = &#34;330&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analysis of political data is a gateway course of political methodology and is compulsory for students in Political Science.&#xA;The course introduces students to statistical and econometric knowledge for the analysis of quantitative data and provides a basis for more advanced statistical methods.&#xA;After covering the fundamental concepts of statistics, such as probability and distributions, we will explore the classical normal linear regression model and its assumptions.&#xA;We will also discuss the consequences and remedies for violations of these assumptions, including omitted variables, heteroscedasticity, autocorrelation, and endogeneity.&#xA;If time permits, we will further talk about the use and interpretation of continuous, ordinal, nominal, and indicator variables, variable interactions, missing data and basic models for limited dependent variables.&#xA;Along the way and primarily in the lab session, students will learn the basics of data collection, organization and management, measurement, data visualization and display, and univariate, bivariate and multivariate descriptive statistics in R.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Public Policy | 公共政策分析 (30700953)</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/01-analysis_of_public_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/01-analysis_of_public_policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.gif&#34; width = &#34;350&#34; height = &#34;330&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analysis of Public Policy: Perspectives and Methods focuses on empirical policy evaluation.&#xA;The course introduces a political scientist view and a series of modern empirical methods into public policy analyses.&#xA;Students will learn not only the fundamental analytic theories for public policy evaluation but also tools such as case study, survey, experiments, and big-data analysis, that can be used to analyze different types of policies.&#xA;In every topic, we will include real-life cases to illustrate how the theories and method can be applied.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Policies | 理解公共政策 (10700193)</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/01-understanding_public_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/01-understanding_public_policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.gif&#34; width = &#34;350&#34; height = &#34;330&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Policies are everywhere in the modern society.&#xA;They serve as the tie between the rulers and ruled and the means to steer collective actions for the given goals.&#xA;In this sense, the ability to understand where policy comes from and how it runs and ends has become a crucial quality of the potential successors and leaders.&#xA;&lt;em&gt;Understanding Public Policies: Interdisciplinary Perspectives and Case Illustrations&lt;/em&gt; is the place you cultivate this quality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning R with Dr. Hu and His Friends | 计算社会科学编程语言证书项目（R语言)</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/04-r-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/method-series/04-r-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I created the &amp;ldquo;Learning R with Dr. Hu and His Friends&amp;rdquo; workshop series to help students without programming background to enjoy the convenience and efficiency programming (esp. based on R) can brings to their academic lives.&#xA;The workshop series include 18 episodes that covers topics from fundamental data cleaning to Bayesian analysis and machine learning.&#xA;This is a year-long program and free to access by all the Tsinghua community offline and others online.&#xA;I also build up an R package &lt;code&gt;drhur&lt;/code&gt; to assist the lectures and off-course practices.&#xA;One can learn how to download and use the package from &#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;/software/drhur&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or in its own &#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sammo3182.github.io/drhur/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Politics | 城市政治学</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/03-urban-politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/03-urban-politics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.gif&#34; width = &#34;300&#34; height = &#34;250&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This course concentrates on the dominant force of human modernization&amp;mdash;the cities. From  a view of political science, the course discuss the macro and micro politics among heterogeneous cities together with specific topics of urban governance. The course is on building. More information will be available soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;preview-slides&#34;&gt;Preview Slides&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#preview-slides&#34;&gt;&lt;svg class=&#34;anchor-symbol&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; height=&#34;26&#34; width=&#34;26&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 22 22&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;path d=&#34;M0 0h24v24H0z&#34; fill=&#34;currentColor&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&#xA;      &lt;path d=&#34;M3.9 12c0-1.71 1.39-3.1 3.1-3.1h4V7H7c-2.76.0-5 2.24-5 5s2.24 5 5 5h4v-1.9H7c-1.71.0-3.1-1.39-3.1-3.1zM8 13h8v-2H8v2zm9-6h-4v1.9h4c1.71.0 3.1 1.39 3.1 3.1s-1.39 3.1-3.1 3.1h-4V17h4c2.76.0 5-2.24 5-5s-2.24-5-5-5z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TBA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professionalism &amp; Competence in Social Science | 社会科学专业化与能力提升研讨课</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/03-professionalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/method-series/03-professionalism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.png&#34; width = &#34;250&#34; height = &#34;200&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Seminar aims to deepen students&amp;rsquo; grasp of social science research&amp;rsquo;s professional aspects and boost their academic and professional competitiveness.&#xA;The curriculum bifurcates into guiding dissertation development and enhancing personal ability demonstration in professional contexts, with a strong focus on political science for case studies.&#xA;This compulsory course for political science graduate students also welcomes other social sciences, promoting interdisciplinary synergy to foster talents for the interdisciplinary-AI era.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governance Big Data | 政务大数据 (80700673)</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/02-goverance_big_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/method-series/02-goverance_big_data/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.jpg&#34; width = &#34;250&#34; height = &#34;200&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Course about how to use big data to investigate governance issues.&#xA;This is an advanced method course. Recommend students who already finished Analysis of Political Data (70700173) or basic statistics/econometric to take.&#xA;I co-instructed the course with Dr. MENG Tianguang.&#xA;The following list are the lectures I usually give for this course:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Research Principles and Method Basis for Big Data Analysis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leading the Focus: Data Visualization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Latent Variable Basic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Latent Variable Advanced&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duration Analysis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Foundations of Text Analysis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Text Analysis in Practice&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Network Analysis: A Methodological Shift&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Network Analysis: Ego and Complete Network Analysis&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本课程拟开设出面向全校社会科学和管理学专业研究生层次的大数据分析应用型课程。课程内容将横跨社会科学和数据科学两个研究领域，涵盖政治学、社会学、管理学、统计学、数据科学等多个学科的理论知识和实用技术。课程目的在于提高大数据时代学生的数据应用意识、建立数据思维、了解前沿方法，以及掌握有关数据采集、处理、分析和解释的基本原理和方法。课程将结合公共管理、司法开放、政治传播、社会治理等政务大数据应用的实际案例，提升学生对大数据方法的应用能力，为学生将大数据方法应用于具体研究打下基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political Culture | 政治文化</title>
      <link>/course/substantive-series/02-principles_of_politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/course/substantive-series/02-principles_of_politics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured.jpg&#34; width = &#34;250&#34; height = &#34;300&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the &amp;ldquo;Political Culture&amp;rdquo; section of the &amp;ldquo;Principles of Politics&amp;rdquo; course led by Dr. MENG Tianguang. The lecture is still an ongoing project. More materials will be available soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;preview-slides&#34;&gt;Preview Slides&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#preview-slides&#34;&gt;&lt;svg class=&#34;anchor-symbol&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; height=&#34;26&#34; width=&#34;26&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 22 22&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;path d=&#34;M0 0h24v24H0z&#34; fill=&#34;currentColor&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&#xA;      &lt;path d=&#34;M3.9 12c0-1.71 1.39-3.1 3.1-3.1h4V7H7c-2.76.0-5 2.24-5 5s2.24 5 5 5h4v-1.9H7c-1.71.0-3.1-1.39-3.1-3.1zM8 13h8v-2H8v2zm9-6h-4v1.9h4c1.71.0 3.1 1.39 3.1 3.1s-1.39 3.1-3.1 3.1h-4V17h4c2.76.0 5-2.24 5-5s-2.24-5-5-5z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TBA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptive Inequality       
不平等认知
</title>
      <link>/project/inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/inequality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;260&#34; height = &#34;330&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project delves into socioeconomic disparities, examining the systematic differences in income, assets, mobility, and access to resources among citizens.&#xA;Our team is interested in the impact, pathways, and mechanisms of this structural property on the political decisions and behaviors of individuals and groups.&#xA;Specifically, the project seeks to understand the dimensions of inequality that people recognize and how this recognition influences their political awareness, preferences, and choices.&#xA;Furthermore, it investigates the origins of the public&amp;rsquo;s perceptions of inequality: what&amp;mdash;or perhaps &lt;em&gt;who&lt;/em&gt;&amp;mdash;influence these perceptions?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political Involvement       
政治“内卷”
</title>
      <link>/project/poliinvolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/poliinvolve/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;350&#34; height = &#34;250&#34; align=&#34;left&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project focuses on the structure of political engagements and their resonance within contemporary society.&#xA;We investigate the construction of political interests and cognition among today&amp;rsquo;s citizens, their modes of political participation in the digital era, and the interplay between public attitudes, opinions, and the processes of politicization and modernization.&#xA;This project is particularly concerned with the implications of public expression and involvement in sociopolitical matters for the individuals involved, as well as for society and the state at large.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political Linguistics   
政治语言学
</title>
      <link>/project/polilingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/polilingua/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;260&#34; height = &#34;200&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Language stands as a quintessential attribute of humanity.&#xA;The enduring debate over whether language shapes thought or vice versa has captivated the greatest minds across history.&#xA;Yet, the role of language in the political sphere remains underexplored.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Approaching from an empirical perspective, this project aims to uncover the impacts of linguistic relativity and language policy on the dynamics between government and the public, as well as on the formation and reformation of collective political consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State and its Audience    
国家与它的受众
</title>
      <link>/project/policommu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/policommu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;260&#34; height = &#34;330&#34; align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Individuals are not passive in their responses to the dominant cultural actions of their own and other countries.&#xA;Despite appearing significantly weaker in the face of powerful state propaganda machinery, they retain sufficient agency to &lt;strong&gt;identify&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;understand&lt;/strong&gt; political propaganda, and to some extent, &lt;strong&gt;influence&lt;/strong&gt; its impact on themselves.&#xA;We are particularly interested in how this process from the macro to the micro level is realized.&#xA;This interest distinguishes our research team&amp;rsquo;s perspective from the political communication and political socialization studies that focus primarily on the state side and commnicational paths.&#xA;Our work delves deeper into the receivers&amp;rsquo; responses, exploring their feelings, comprehension, and actions in response to political messages from the government.&#xA;A fundamental yet complex question underpins this research: who constitutes the audience for the state authority (in media environment, formal and informal education, international society) and why?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>interplot</title>
      <link>/software/interplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/software/interplot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Solt, Frederick, and &lt;strong&gt;Yue Hu&lt;/strong&gt;. 2015. interplot: Plot the Coefficients of Variables in Interaction Terms. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/web/packages/interplot/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.r-pkg.org/badges/version/interplot&#34; alt=&#34;CRAN version&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/grand-total/interplot&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/interplot?color=orange&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;interplot&lt;/code&gt; is a tool for plotting the conditional coefficients (&amp;ldquo;marginal effects&amp;rdquo;) of variables included in multiplicative interaction terms. The function plots the changes in the coefficient of one variable in a two-way interaction term conditional on the value of the other included variable. The resulting plot also includes simulated 95% confidential intervals of these coefficients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotwhisker</title>
      <link>/software/dotwhisker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/software/dotwhisker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Solt, Frederick, and &lt;strong&gt;Yue Hu&lt;/strong&gt;. 2015. dotwhisker: Dot-and-Whisker Plots of Regression Results. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/web/packages/dotwhisker/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.r-pkg.org/badges/version/dotwhisker&#34; alt=&#34;CRAN version&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/grand-total/dotwhisker&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/dotwhisker?color=orange&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;dotwhisker&lt;/code&gt; is an R package for quickly and easily generating dot-and-whisker plots of regression results, either directly from model objects or from tidy data frames. It provides a convenient way to create highly customizable plots for presenting and comparing statistics. It can be used to plot coefficients or other estimates (e.g., predicted probabilities) within a model or compare them across different models. The estimates are presented as dots with confidence interval whiskers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>regioncode</title>
      <link>/software/regioncode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/software/regioncode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hu, Yue&lt;/strong&gt; et al. 2020. regioncode: Convert Region Names and Division Codes of China Over Years. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/package=regioncode&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.r-pkg.org/badges/version/regioncode&#34; alt=&#34;CRAN version&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/grand-total/regioncode&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/regioncode?color=orange&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inspired by Vincent Arel-Bundock&amp;rsquo;s well-known &#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://joss.theoj.org/papers/10.21105/joss.00848&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;countrycode&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we created &lt;code&gt;regioncode&lt;/code&gt; to achieve similar functions specifically for China studies. &lt;code&gt;regioncode&lt;/code&gt; enables seamlessly converting regions&amp;rsquo; formal names, common-used names, and administrative division codes between each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To install:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest released version: &lt;code&gt;install.packages(&amp;quot;regioncode&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest developing version: &lt;code&gt;remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/regioncode&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More details are available at:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>drhur</title>
      <link>/software/drhur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/software/drhur/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yue Hu&lt;/strong&gt;. 2016. drhur: Learning R with Dr. Hu. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/package=drhur&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.r-pkg.org/badges/version/drhur&#34; alt=&#34;CRAN version&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/grand-total/drhur&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/drhur?color=orange&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;drhur&lt;/code&gt; is pedagogical software make the R learners&amp;rsquo; life a little bit easier and more happily and a supplementary courseware for Dr. Yue Hu&amp;rsquo;s R program lectures.&#xA;The tutorials included are crystallized during Dr. Hu&amp;rsquo;s online and offline R workshop.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To install:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest release version: &lt;code&gt;install.packages(&amp;quot;drhur&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest version: &lt;code&gt;remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/drhur&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More details are available at here:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>drhutools</title>
      <link>/software/drhutools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/software/drhutools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A toolbox for writing an academic paper with rmarkdown. The tools includes data analyses, visualization, and documenting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To install:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest released version: &lt;code&gt;install.packages(&amp;quot;drhutools&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest developing version: &lt;code&gt;remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/drhutools&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pewdata</title>
      <link>/software/pewdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/software/pewdata/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;featured-hex.png&#34; width = &#34;134.435&#34; height = &#34;155.25&#34;  align=&#34;right&#34; /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Solt, Frederick, and &lt;strong&gt;Yue Hu&lt;/strong&gt;. 2016. pewdata: Reproducible Retrieval of Pew Research Center Datasets. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cran.r-project.org/package=pewdata&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.r-pkg.org/badges/version/pewdata&#34; alt=&#34;CRAN version&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/grand-total/pewdata&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://cranlogs.r-pkg.org/badges/pewdata?color=orange&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://travis-ci.org/fsolt/pewdata&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://travis-ci.org/fsolt/pewdata.svg?branch=master&#34; alt=&#34;Travis-CI Build Status&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;pewdata&lt;/code&gt; is an R package that provides reproducible, programmatic access to survey datasets from the &#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pewresearch.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Pew Research Center&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To install:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest released version: &lt;code&gt;install.packages(&amp;quot;pewdata&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;the latest development version:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;background-color:#fff;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-R&#34; data-lang=&#34;R&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#cf222e&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#0550ae&#34;&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#6639ba&#34;&gt;require&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;ghit&lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;))&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;color:#6639ba&#34;&gt;install.packages&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#0a3069&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;ghit&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;ghit&lt;span style=&#34;color:#0550ae&#34;&gt;::&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#6639ba&#34;&gt;install_github&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#0a3069&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;fsolt/pewdata&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#1f2328&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note that &lt;code&gt;pewdata&lt;/code&gt; depends on the Firefox browser; if you don&amp;rsquo;t already have it installed on your machine, &#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mozilla.org/firefox&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;get it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above.&#xA;See form.html in the layouts folder.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.&#xA;**&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/contributors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;http://desiree.rbind.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Desirée De Leon &amp;#x1f992;&lt;/a&gt; (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.garrickadenbuie.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Garrick Aden-Buie &amp;#x1f9d9;&lt;/a&gt; (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.allisonhorst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Allison Horst &amp;#x1f415;&lt;/a&gt; (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot &amp;#x1f994;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/license/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The content of my website is released under a &#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;center&gt;&#xA;&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-creative-commons fa-2x&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-creative-commons-by fa-2x&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-creative-commons-sa fa-2x&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;&lt;/center&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
