<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Identity &amp; Urban Governance</title>
      <link>/project/urbanpoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/urbanpoli/</guid>
      <description>Urban citizens are not only the demographic distributions in urban areas or objects ruled by the urban governments but active participants of urban governance and leading constructors of the state-society relationship. If regarding government policies as the responses of the public demands, I am interested in the responses of citizens with heterogeneous identities to these responses. Furthermore, I would like to evaluate the efficiency of the same policy tools on different groups of citizens in different types of cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inequality &amp; Opinions</title>
      <link>/project/inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/inequality/</guid>
      <description>Socioeconomic inequality includes systematic discrepancies among different groups of citizens in income, assets, mobility, accessible resources, etc. I am interested in the effects, paths, and mechanisms of this structural property on individual and group political cognition and attitudes.
Published Studies     Solt, Frederick, Yue Hu, Kevan Hudson, Jungmin Song, Dong &amp;lsquo;Erico&amp;rsquo; Yu. 2017. “Economic Inequality and Class Consciousness.” The Journal of Politics 79(3): 1079–83.
———. 2016. “Economic Inequality and Belief in Meritocracy in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Linguistics</title>
      <link>/project/polilingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/polilingua/</guid>
      <description>Language is the fundamental feature of human beings. The debate of whether does language shapes thoughts or the other way around has inspires the greatest theorists and scientists throughout the human history. I aim to contribute to this classic topic from a view of political science. Using experimental and observed studies, I strive to identify the language effect in mass political cognition and linguistic relativity in sociopolitical behaviors and attitudes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Persuasion</title>
      <link>/project/policommu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/policommu/</guid>
      <description>I am interested in an age of the Internet and new media, how state media conduct their functions of political persuasion and political mobilization. I also wonder about how citizens consider and respond to state media and how they affect modern citizens&#39; political cognition especially in non-Western countries.
Published Studies     Jiang, Qiaolei, Shiyu Liu, Yue Hu, and Jing Xu. 2022. “Social Media for Health Campaign and Solidarity Among Chinses Fandom Publics During the Covid-19 Pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
