<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Political Communication</title>
      <link>/project/policommu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/policommu/</guid>
      <description>People do not merely respond to the outside world; they recognize, process, and make choices. I am interested in how this psychological process is achieved within media interactions among the sender, carrier, and receiver. This also makes my research different from the prevalent political-communication studies that focus on the content and means of the media. Instead, I focus more on how people respond to them, for instance, what the audience actually feels, understands, and does when they are exposed to a political message from the government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Linguistics</title>
      <link>/project/polilingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/polilingua/</guid>
      <description>Language is the fundamental feature of human beings. The debate of whether does language shapes thoughts or the other way around has inspires the greatest theorists and scientists throughout the human history. Nevertheless, the importance of language in political lives has not been well studied yet.
Cutting in from an empirical angle, I strive to identify the influences of linguistic relativity and language planning in the government-mass relationship and the (re)construction of mass political cognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Response</title>
      <link>/project/poliresponse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/poliresponse/</guid>
      <description>Disproportionate scholarly attention in the studies of the government-mass relationship focused on the government&amp;rsquo;s responses (motivations and means) to public demands. Less research explores what happens next. However, in real politics, the governments often fall into the curse that what they do mismatches what the public wants. I unbox this puzzle by investigating how the public responds to the government&amp;rsquo;s response. Several focused questions include: what do the masses learn from the government&amp;rsquo;s decisions and actions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socioeconomic Inequality</title>
      <link>/project/inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/inequality/</guid>
      <description>Socioeconomic inequality includes systematic discrepancies among citizens in income, assets, mobility, accessible resources, etc. I am interested in this structural property&amp;rsquo;s effects, paths, and mechanisms on individual and group political decisions and behaviors. In particular, how do people recognize inequality (what aspects of inequality)? How does their awareness and understanding of inequality affect their political cognition, preferences, and decisions? Even more interestingly, what (or&amp;hellip;who) forms the masses&#39; inequality perceptions?
Selected Publications     Solt, Frederick, Yue Hu, Kevan Hudson, Jungmin Song, Dong &amp;lsquo;Erico&amp;rsquo; Yu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
