<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects 项目 on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects 项目 on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Perceptive Inequality       
不平等认知
</title>
      <link>/project/inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/inequality/</guid>
      <description>This project delves into socioeconomic disparities, examining the systematic differences in income, assets, mobility, and access to resources among citizens. Our team is interested in the impact, pathways, and mechanisms of this structural property on the political decisions and behaviors of individuals and groups. Specifically, the project seeks to understand the dimensions of inequality that people recognize and how this recognition influences their political awareness, preferences, and choices. Furthermore, it investigates the origins of the public&amp;rsquo;s perceptions of inequality: what&amp;mdash;or perhaps who&amp;mdash;influence these perceptions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Involvement       
政治“内卷”
</title>
      <link>/project/poliinvolve/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/poliinvolve/</guid>
      <description>This project focuses on the structure of political engagements and their resonance within contemporary society. We investigate the construction of political interests and cognition among today&amp;rsquo;s citizens, their modes of political participation in the digital era, and the interplay between public attitudes, opinions, and the processes of politicization and modernization. This project is particularly concerned with the implications of public expression and involvement in sociopolitical matters for the individuals involved, as well as for society and the state at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Linguistics   
政治语言学
</title>
      <link>/project/polilingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/polilingua/</guid>
      <description>Language stands as a quintessential attribute of humanity. The enduring debate over whether language shapes thought or vice versa has captivated the greatest minds across history. Yet, the role of language in the political sphere remains underexplored.
Approaching from an empirical perspective, this project aims to uncover the impacts of linguistic relativity and language policy on the dynamics between government and the public, as well as on the formation and reformation of collective political consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State and its Audience    
国家与它的受众
</title>
      <link>/project/policommu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/policommu/</guid>
      <description>Individuals are not passive in their responses to the dominant cultural actions of their own and other countries. Despite appearing significantly weaker in the face of powerful state propaganda machinery, they retain sufficient agency to identify and understand political propaganda, and to some extent, influence its impact on themselves. We are particularly interested in how this process from the macro to the micro level is realized. This interest distinguishes our research team&amp;rsquo;s perspective from the political communication and political socialization studies that focus primarily on the state side and commnicational paths.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
