<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>methodology on Hu Yue</title>
    <link>/categories/methodology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in methodology on Hu Yue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/methodology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Political Data | 政治数据分析</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/01-analysis_of_poli_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/method-series/01-analysis_of_poli_data/</guid>
      <description>Analysis of political data is a gateway course of political methodology and is compulsory for students in Political Science. The course introduces students to statistical and econometric knowledge for the analysis of quantitative data and provides a basis for more advanced statistical methods. After covering the fundamental concepts of statistics, such as probability and distributions, we will explore the classical normal linear regression model and its assumptions. We will also discuss the consequences and remedies for violations of these assumptions, including omitted variables, heteroscedasticity, autocorrelation, and endogeneity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning R with Dr. Hu and His Friends | R语言工作坊</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/03-r-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/method-series/03-r-workshop/</guid>
      <description>I created the &amp;ldquo;Learning R with Dr. Hu and His Friends&amp;rdquo; workshop series to help students without programming background to enjoy the convenience and efficiency programming (esp. based on R) can brings to their academic lives. The workshop series include 18 episodes that covers topics from fundamental data cleaning to Bayesian analysis and machine learning. This is a year-long program and free to access by all the Tsinghua community offline and others online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance Big Data | 政务大数据</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/02-goverance_big_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/method-series/02-goverance_big_data/</guid>
      <description>Course about how to use big data to investigate governance issues. This is an advanced method course. Recommend students who already finished Analysis of Political Data (70700173) or basic statistics/econometric to take. I co-instructed the course with Dr. MENG Tianguang. The following list are the lectures I usually give for this course:
 Research Principles and Method Basis for Big Data Analysis Leading the Focus: Data Visualization Latent Variable Basic Latent Variable Advanced Duration Analysis Foundations of Text Analysis Text Analysis in Practice Network Analysis: A Methodological Shift Network Analysis: Ego and Complete Network Analysis  本课程拟开设出面向全校社会科学和管理学专业研究生层次的大数据分析应用型课程。课程内容将横跨社会科学和数据科学两个研究领域，涵盖政治学、社会学、管理学、统计学、数据科学等多个学科的理论知识和实用技术。课程目的在于提高大数据时代学生的数据应用意识、建立数据思维、了解前沿方法，以及掌握有关数据采集、处理、分析和解释的基本原理和方法。课程将结合公共管理、司法开放、政治传播、社会治理等政务大数据应用的实际案例，提升学生对大数据方法的应用能力，为学生将大数据方法应用于具体研究打下基础。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inequality &amp; Opinions</title>
      <link>/project/inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/inequality/</guid>
      <description>Socioeconomic inequality includes systematic discrepancies among different groups of citizens in income, assets, mobility, accessible resources, etc. I am interested in the effects, paths, and mechanisms of this structural property on individual and group political cognition and attitudes.
Published Studies     Solt, Frederick, Yue Hu, Kevan Hudson, Jungmin Song, Dong &amp;lsquo;Erico&amp;rsquo; Yu. 2017. “Economic Inequality and Class Consciousness.” The Journal of Politics 79(3): 1079–83.
———. 2016. “Economic Inequality and Belief in Meritocracy in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Method Courses for &#34;Non-Math&#34; Students</title>
      <link>/course/method-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/course/method-series/</guid>
      <description>** No content below YAML for the series _index. This file is a leaf bundle, and provides settings for the listing page layout and sidebar content.**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Linguistics</title>
      <link>/project/polilingua/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/polilingua/</guid>
      <description>Language is the fundamental feature of human beings. The debate of whether does language shapes thoughts or the other way around has inspires the greatest theorists and scientists throughout the human history. I aim to contribute to this classic topic from a view of political science. Using experimental and observed studies, I strive to identify the language effect in mass political cognition and linguistic relativity in sociopolitical behaviors and attitudes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Persuasion</title>
      <link>/project/policommu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/policommu/</guid>
      <description>I am interested in an age of the Internet and new media, how state media conduct their functions of political persuasion and political mobilization. I also wonder about how citizens consider and respond to state media and how they affect modern citizens&#39; political cognition especially in non-Western countries.
Published Studies     Jiang, Qiaolei, Shiyu Liu, Yue Hu, and Jing Xu. 2022. “Social Media for Health Campaign and Solidarity Among Chinses Fandom Publics During the Covid-19 Pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>interplot</title>
      <link>/software/interplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/interplot/</guid>
      <description>Solt, Frederick, and Yue Hu. 2015. interplot: Plot the Coefficients of Variables in Interaction Terms. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  interplot is a tool for plotting the conditional coefficients (&amp;ldquo;marginal effects&amp;rdquo;) of variables included in multiplicative interaction terms. The function plots the changes in the coefficient of one variable in a two-way interaction term conditional on the value of the other included variable. The resulting plot also includes simulated 95% confidential intervals of these coefficients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dotwhisker</title>
      <link>/software/dotwhisker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/dotwhisker/</guid>
      <description>Solt, Frederick, and Yue Hu. 2015. dotwhisker: Dot-and-Whisker Plots of Regression Results. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
 dotwhisker is an R package for quickly and easily generating dot-and-whisker plots of regression results, either directly from model objects or from tidy data frames. It provides a convenient way to create highly customizable plots for presenting and comparing statistics. It can be used to plot coefficients or other estimates (e.g., predicted probabilities) within a model or compare them across different models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>regioncode</title>
      <link>/software/regioncode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/regioncode/</guid>
      <description>Hu, Yue et al. 2020. regioncode: Convert Region Names and Division Codes of China Over Years. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  Inspired by Vincent Arel-Bundock&amp;rsquo;s well-known countrycode, we created regioncode to achieve similar functions specifically for China studies. regioncode enables seamlessly converting regions&#39; formal names, common-used names, and administrative division codes between each other.
To install:
 the latest released version: install.packages(&amp;quot;regioncode&amp;quot;). the latest developing version: remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/regioncode&amp;quot;).  More details are available at:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drhur</title>
      <link>/software/drhur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/drhur/</guid>
      <description>Yue Hu. 2016. drhur: Learning R with Dr. Hu. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  drhur is pedagogical software make the R learners&#39; life a little bit easier and more happily and a supplementary courseware for Dr. Yue Hu&amp;rsquo;s R program lectures. The tutorials included are crystallized during Dr. Hu&amp;rsquo;s online and offline R workshop.
To install:
 the latest release version: install.packages(&amp;quot;drhur&amp;quot;).   the latest version: remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/drhur&amp;quot;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drhutools</title>
      <link>/software/drhutools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/drhutools/</guid>
      <description>A toolbox for writing an academic paper with rmarkdown. The tools includes data analyses, visualization, and documenting.
To install:
 the latest released version: install.packages(&amp;quot;drhutools&amp;quot;). the latest developing version: remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;sammo3182/drhutools&amp;quot;).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pewdata</title>
      <link>/software/pewdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/pewdata/</guid>
      <description>Solt, Frederick, and Yue Hu. 2016. pewdata: Reproducible Retrieval of Pew Research Center Datasets. The Comprehensive R Archive Network (CRAN).
  
pewdata is an R package that provides reproducible, programmatic access to survey datasets from the Pew Research Center.
To install:
 the latest released version: install.packages(&amp;quot;pewdata&amp;quot;) the latest development version:  if (!require(ghit)) install.packages(&amp;#34;ghit&amp;#34;) ghit::install_github(&amp;#34;fsolt/pewdata&amp;#34;) Note that pewdata depends on the Firefox browser; if you don&amp;rsquo;t already have it installed on your machine, get it here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
